Guide to the Visual AIDS Records MSS.503
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. Projects and Exhibitions, 1989-2017; 20 Linear Feet in 25 manuscript boxes, 5 small manuscript boxes, 3 oversized flat boxes, 4 flat-file folders, and 9 items in 3 shared boxes; 176.6 Megabytes in 80 computer files; 3 VHS; 1 audiocassette; 1 U-matic; 2 Betacam
  - The Ribbon Project -- U.S. Postage Stamp and Related, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - The Ribbon Project -- Responses to New Yorker Magazine Article, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - The Ribbon Project -- The Red Ribbon Report Newsletter, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - The Ribbon Project -- Drawings of Unknown Art Installation Using Ribbons, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - The Ribbon Project -- Description of BBC Radio Show Episode from From This Moment On, circa 2003 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - The Ribbon Project -- Card Containing Red Ribbon, Celebrating Its Addition into MoMA Permanent Design Collection, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - The Ribbon Project -- Red Ribbon Cloth and Plastic Wall Hanging, undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - The Ribbon Project -- Draft of Advertisement for the Project Including Broadside Images, undated (Flat-file-folder 4 left)
  - New York Gay & Lesbian Pride March -- Award for Best Use of Theme, June 28, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Dolls Benefit Sale -- Information Sheet, July 18, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Celebrity Ribbon Cavalcade -- Event Photographs, Promotional Material, Meeting Notes, December 1, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
  - Lesbian and Gay Pride March (June), and Celebrity Ribbon Cavalcade (December) -- Video Recording, June 28 and December 1, 1992 (Box 78, U-matic 503_0012)
  - Love Shack Pop-up Store -- Proposal, Correspondence, Notes, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Patrick Burton Publishing Project, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Exhibit -- Brian Weil: The AIDS Photographs -- Planning and Background Material, 1992-1997 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Broadsides and Day Without Art -- Slide Images of Posters, 1990-1998 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Broadsides -- Expenses, Order Form, Descriptions, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Broadsides -- Descriptions, Mailing Lists, Copies of Images, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Broadsides -- Glen Ligon -- Poster, Proof Images, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 13, Box 65, Folder 5, Box Shared Fales 122, Folder 6)
  - Broadsides -- Barbara Kruger -- Posters, Proofs, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 14, Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Broadsides -- Barbara Kruger -- T-shirt Printed with Poster Image, circa 1992 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Broadsides -- Promotional Information Sheets, Order Forms, Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Broadsides -- Visual AIDS Artists Caucus' "This is One Week's Medication for a Person with AIDS…" -- Images, Proofs, Original Photograph, Poster, Print Advertisements, 1993-1996 (Box 11, Folder 16, Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Broadsides -- Visual AIDS Artists Caucus' "This is One Week's Medication for a Person with AIDS…" -- Proof, 1993 (Box Shared Fales 122, Folder 5)
  - Broadsides -- John Giorno -- Poster, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Broadsides -- Adrian Kellard -- Edited Poster Proofs and Prints, circa 1993 (Box Shared Fales 109, Folder 16, Box Shared Fales 122, Folder 4)
  - Broadsides -- Adamo Yuri Melaney -- Poster, Proofs, Original, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 18, Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Broadsides -- Correspondence, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Broadsides -- Roberto Juarez, William Cullum, Steed Taylor -- Posters, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Broadsides -- Flier Calling for New Poster Proposals, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Broadsides -- Mike Parker -- Poster, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Broadsides -- Bradford Branch, Copy Berg -- Posters, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Broadsides -- Collection of Older Posters (1990s) and New, Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Broadsides -- Distribution Survey, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Broadsides -- William Powhida Poster, Letter, Information Sheet, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Broadsides -- Promotional Flier, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - D.A.D.A. Party -- Promotional Material, February 1, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Celebrity Ribbon Cavalcade -- Tickets, Invitations, Correspondence, May 24, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - "Seeing Red: The Ribbon (Pro or Con?)" Discussion and Related Artists' AIDS Broadsides Exhibit, June 2, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Celebrity Ribbon Cavalcade at New York City Lesbian and Gay Pride Parade -- Information Sheets, June 27, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Exhibit at MoMA -- Projects: In Memory of… -- Original Memorial Wall Cards, November 22 - December 1993 (Box 70, Box 71, Box 72, Box 73)
  - Exhibit at MoMA -- Projects: In Memory of… -- Original Memorial Wall Cards, November 22 - December 1993 (Box 74, Box 75, Box 76, Box 77)
  - The Dada Ball -- Planning Documentation, Promotional Material, Poster, October 11, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 5-6, Flat-file-folder 6 Left)
  - Hunter Reynolds -- Patina du Prey's Memorial Dress -- Performance Information, Press Clippings, Descriptions of Work, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - "Queer Spaces: Repossessing History" Project -- Proof for Street Signage for the Gay Activists Alliance Location, and an Image of Artwork Containing Chairs, 1994 (Box Shared Fales 109, Folder 17)
  - National Association of Artists' Organizations (NAOO) Conference Panel Discussion "The Artist Living with AIDS" -- Promotional Information, October 14, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Exhibit at God's Love We Deliver -- Notes, Contacts, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Coalition of Peer Educators (COPE) -- Poster Project, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Andrés & Tony Booklet Project -- Booklet, Press Clippings, Correspondence, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Exhibit -- Steed Taylor's Gay Icons: Out, Proud & Large -- Announcement, Image Contact Sheet and Negatives, June 24 - July 24, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 12, Box Shared Fales 122, Folder 9)
  - Exhibit -- No Show: Art for Day Without Art -- Catalog, November 7 - December 7, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Benefit Dinner Party Honoring Frank Moore -- Correspondence, Promotional Material, November 8, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Unknown Exhibit Opening and Dinner -- Slide Images, November 15, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - ArtsWire Current Project Description, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Gallery (+) Positive -- Partnership Documentation, General Information, 1996-1998, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Exhibit -- The Cocktail -- Promotional Flier, Notes, June 18, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Exhibit -- Not Sacred -- Promotional Material, Notes, Slide Images of Artworks Installed, June 23 - October 17, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Mapping No Boundaries Projects -- Agreement, Proposal Description, Correspondence, November 1997 - February 1998 (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
  - Mapping No Boundaries Projects -- "Art, AIDS, Action" Fundraiser Promotional Material, Booklets, Press Release, November 1997 - February 1998 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Mapping No Boundaries Projects -- Exhibit What Now? Promotional Material, Artists' Statements, Correspondence, November 6 - December 31, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Mapping No Boundaries Projects -- Funding, Requests, and Related, November 6 - December 31, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Mapping No Boundaries Projects -- Catalog/Book and Related, November 6 - December 31, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Mapping No Boundaries Projects -- Venues Correspondence and Related, November 6 - December 31, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Mapping No Boundaries Projects -- Midtown, Chelsea, and SoHo Walk Maps and Related, November 6 - December 31, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Mapping No Boundaries Projects -- T-Shirt, November 6 - December 31, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Exhibit -- Positive Art Exposed at Gershwin Hotel-- Midtown, Chelsea, and SoHo Walk Maps and Related, December 1, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Benjamin Trimmier Exhibit Proposal, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - AIDS Monument Committee Material, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Time Capsule Project -- Description, Correspondence, Completed Forms, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Unknown Project -- Photographs, Signed Consent Forms, Promotional Poster Sketches, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Abbott Laboratories Calendars -- Planning Material, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Unknown Event at L.U.R.E. -- Photographs and Negatives, January 29, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Abbott Laboratories Party -- Photographs, February 1998 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Benefit Exhibit for Visual AIDS at Studio 24 -- Promotional Card, June 25 - July 3, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Visual AIDS' 10th Anniversary 100x100 Benefit at Hunt Slonem Loft -- Photographs, Correspondence, Planning Documents, November 17, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Unknown Event -- Photographs and Negatives, circa 1998 (Box 14, Folder 7-8)
  - Cable Positive Tony Cox Fund for HIV/AIDS Local Programming -- Funding Material, Questionnaire, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Positively Art Wall Calendars, 1998-2001 (Box 68, Folder 2-5)
  - Positively Art Calendar-Related -- Press Clippings, Planning Notes, Completed Forms, Project Description, 1998-2006 (Box 14, Folder 10-14)
  - Visual AIDS Benefits Scrapbook Material -- Invitations, Promotional Material, Images, 1998-2012 (Box 14, Folder 15, Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Postcards from the Edge Benefits -- Planning Documents, Invitations, Photographs, Press Releases, 1998-2017 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
  - Visual AIDS My Bloody Valentine Benefit at L.U.R.E. -- Planning, Promotional Material, Photographs, February 11, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 4-6)
  - Desire -- Installation and Opening Party Photographs, Promotional Material, Planning Material, June 12-26, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 7-8)
  - Unknown Event Interiors and Staff Photographs, August 1999 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Exhibit and Book -- Bearing Witness -- Press Release, Promotional Material, Book/Catalog, Model Release Forms, Funding Requests, Artwork Images, Book Proof, September 8-15, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 1-6)
  - Exhibit -- Bodies of Resistance -- Proposal, Budgets, Promotional Material, Press Clippings, Installation Photographs and Directions, Proofs and Final Catalog, December 1, 1999 - January 31, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 7-12, Box 17, Folder 1-9)
  - Fiesta del Siglo Event -- Planning Material, Guest Forms, Lists, December 31, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 10-11)
  - Institute of Cultural Inquiry Project -- 1998 Wrap-Up Layout Draft Sheet, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Web Gallery Press Clipping, The Body Web Partnership Material, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 2-4)
  - Virtual AIDS Spring Benefit -- Announcement, May 3, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Exhibit -- Our Wandering Thoughts -- Curated by Students of the Arts Benefit All Coalition Alternative (ABACA) Curatorial Studies class, June 13-24, 2000
    - Promotional Paper Material (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Video Recording (Box 78, Vhs 503_0014)
  - Panel Discussion and Exhibit at Rutgers University -- Photographs, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Monograph Series Funding Project Proposal, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Sida Gráfico Card Project -- Cards, circa 2000 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Exhibit -- Becky Trotter: Pull Up a Chair -- Announcement Card, June 11 - September 15, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Benefit Gallery Opening and Concert, June 18, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Video Positive Project with Bronx Museum of the Arts -- Promotional Material, November 27 - December 1, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Angie Eng Lifesigns AIDS Prevention Program -- Correspondence, Photographs, Budget, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - House of Frame by Frame Fierce Partnership -- Project Descriptions, Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - A Big Fat Hairy Deal Benefit -- Event Planning Files, Promotional Material, Committee Meeting Material, 2002-2004 (Box 18, Folder 15-17, Box 19, Folder 1)
  - A Big Fat Hairy Deal Benefit -- Photographs, 2003; FA_MSS_503_ER_1
  - Robert Blanchon Estate Project -- Exhibit Planning, Book and Catalog Planning, 2002-2010 (Box 19, Folder 2-16, Box 20, Folder 1-9, Box 21, Folder 1-4, Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Delta Sigma Theta Event -- Promotional Flyer, Planning Notes, March 8, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Unknown Event Audio Recording -- "Day 2: Side A / Day 2 Side B", June 3, 2003 (Box Shared Fales 103, Audiocassette 503_0006)
  - Nebraska Artists -- Notes, July 2003 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Share Your Vision Campaign and Exhibit -- Planning Material, Print Advertising, Promotional Material, October 22 - November 1, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 7-10, Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Share Your Vision Campaign and Exhibit -- Funding, Artist, and Jury-Related Correspondence, October 22 - November 1, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 2-8)
  - Share Your Vision Campaign and Exhibit -- Applicant and Winner Lists, Signed Artist Contracts, October 22 - November 1, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 9-10)
  - Share Your Vision Campaign and Exhibit -- Loan Agreements, Installation Plans and Images, Event Planning Material, October 22 - November 1, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 1-7)
  - Share Your Vision Campaign and Exhibit -- Catalog Correspondence, Notes, Drafts, October 22 - November 1, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 8-9, Box 24, Folder 1-5)
  - Share Your Vision Campaign and Exhibit -- Press Clippings, Calendar Production Material, Calendar, October 22 - November 1, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 6-7, Box 25, Folder 1-4)
  - Share Your Vision Campaign and Exhibit -- Poster, Print Advertisements, October 22 - November 1, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 8, Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Share Your Vision Campaign and Exhibit -- HIV Positive Artists Help Raise Awareness about CMV Retinitis, September 2003 (Box 78, Betacam 503_0015)
  - Share Your Vision Campaign and Exhibit -- MS&L, ROCHE, Sharing Your Vision, September 2003 (Box 78, Betacam 503_0016)
  - Share Your Vision Campaign and Exhibit -- Initiative Video Recording, 2003 (Box 78, Vhs 503_0020)
  - "Fight AIDS Not Iraq" Postcard and Related, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - HIV Law Project -- Luis Carle, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Steed Taylor Natal Knot Road Tattoo Project -- Notes, Letter, Description, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Evening with John Dugdale Benefit, December 9, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - GlaxoSmithKline -- Calendars, Artwork Purchases, 2004-2006 (Box 25, Folder 9, Box Shared Fales 109, Folder 18-19)
  - Bronx Museum and Albert Einstein School Project -- Notes, circa 2004 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Visual AIDS Benefit, March 8, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - "Screening HIV: New(ish) Film/Video Considering HIV and the AIDS Pandemic" -- Promotional Fliers, Notes, December 1, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Kermit Berg Exhibit -- Funding Material, Project Description, 2005-2006 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Visual AIDS Programs and Exhibits Listings and Promotional Material, 2005-2017 (Box 25, Folder 14-17, Box 26, Folder 1-2)
  - Visual AIDS Lost & Found Benefit -- Invitations, June 5, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - International AIDS Conference -- Visual AIDS Exhibit Between Ten, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Paul Sedziuk -- Academic Partner Correspondence and Work Files, 2006-2008 (Box 26, Folder 5-6)
  - "Strike!" Visual AIDS Vanguard Awards -- Invitations, Stickers, Shirt, 2006-2009 (Box 26, Folder 7-8, Box 62, Folder 2)
  - "VAVA Voom" Visual AIDS Vanguard Awards -- Invitations, Notes, Programs, 2010-2017 (Box 26, Folder 9, Box 27, Folder 1-2)
  - Marketing Stickers and Postcards -- Sticker: "Love Happened Here" by Nayland Blake, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Marketing Stickers and Postcards -- "AIDS Is Not Over" Theme by Lou Laurita, Nancer Lemoins, and John Chaich, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Marketing Stickers and Postcards -- "AIDS Is Not Over" Theme by Hunter Reynolds and Unknown, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Marketing Stickers and Postcards -- "AIDS Is Not Over" Themed Business Cards "Conception" by Ingrid Tsang, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Marketing Stickers and Postcards -- "For the Record" by Fierce Pussy, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Marketing Cards -- "Rubbers Are Fun" by Michael Mitchel, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Marketing Stickers -- "AIDS"; "Bush AIDS Flag"; "I Tested HIV+ When I was 64…", undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Marketing Sticker -- "Follow Your Nose" by Carrie Moyer, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Marketing Sticker -- "Be Creative But Be Safe..." by Joe De Hoyos, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - AIDS / Art / Work Conference Material, May 30, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Exhibit -- Side x Side -- Information Packet, Press Release, Print Advertisement, June 28 - August 3, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 13, Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Exhibit -- AIDS Awareness Broadsides: 1992-2008 -- Promotional Card, December 1, 2008 - February 27, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Exhibit -- Tainted Love -- Catalog Booklet, Press Clippings, June 4-28, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Exhibit -- You Make Me Feel... Robert Blanchon -- Promotional Card, November 19, 2009 - February 26, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - NADA (New Art Dealers Alliance) Art Fair -- Agreement, Correspondence, December 2009 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Exhibit -- To Believe -- Booklet, Promotional Material, June 3-27, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - "Play Smart" by Visual AIDS Trading Cards, 2010-2017 (Box 27, Folder 19, Box 28, Folder 1)
  - "Play Smart" by Visual AIDS Trading Card Event with Panel Discussion and Artist Signings, 2011 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - "Play Smart" by Visual AIDS Poster of Trading Card Images from 2013-2016 (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Exhibit -- Mixed Messages: A(I)DS, Art + Words -- Promotional Material, Press Clipping, June 2 - July 3, 2011 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Exhibit -- The Sword of Damocles: Selections from Franck Moore Archive Project -- Catalogue Booklet, November 29 - December 23, 2011 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Exhibit -- Undetectable -- Proposal, Promotional Material, Catalog, May 31 - June 30, 2012 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Exhibit -- Remixed Messages -- Promotional Material, Catalog Booklet, July 24 - August 4, 2012 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Exhibit -- Not Over: 25 Years of Visual AIDS -- Promotional Cards, Catalog Booklet, Notes, May - July 2013 (Box 28, Folder 7-8)
  - Listing of Art Workshops for Young Adults, October 2013 - March 2014 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Love Positive Women Project -- Promotional Card, circa 2013-2017 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Exhibit -- Ephemera As Evidence -- Promotional Cards, Catalog Booklet, June 5-29, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Artists Talk -- Promotional Card, circa June 2014 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Project by Visual AIDS for the 25th Anniversary of Day without Art: Alternate Endings -- Promotional Card, December 1-7, 2014 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Publishing -- Duets Series Booklets and Promotional Bookmarks, 2014, 2016 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Publishing -- Hugh Steers: The Complete Paintings Book Launch Promotional Flier, Fall 2015 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Publishing -- Hugh Steers: The Complete Paintings Book, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Publishing -- Publications Listings, circa 2016 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Publishing -- Promotional Bookmarks with Artwork Images, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Exhibit -- Elastic Practice -- Promotional Brochure, June 1 - September 18, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Exhibit -- Party Out of Bounds -- Promotional Card for Party "No Pants No Problem", September 18 - October 10, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Exhibit -- Persons of Interest -- Promotional Cards, June 2 - September 4, 2016 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Exhibit -- Everyday -- Wall Calendar, November 17 - December 10, 2016 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Visual AIDS at La Maison de Sade -- Promotional Card, June 15, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Bitch Party Benefit -- Promotional Card, December 10, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Staff, Artworks, and Event Photographs, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - "Mid-State Positive Voices" Event -- Notes, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Portrait of Unknown Man -- Large Format Negative, undated (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Exhibit -- "Hell's Kitchen" -- Slides of Installation, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Video Recording -- "Kissing Kills" PSA, undated (Box 78, Vhs 503_0017)
  - Posters of Printed Photograph Collages Depicting Male Models in Poses, circa 1980s (Flat-file-folder Temp 1)
- Series III. Day With(out) Art, 1989-2013; 15 Linear Feet in 20 manuscript boxes, 3 oversize flat boxes, 8 flat-file folders, and 9 items in 3 shared boxes; 2 audiocassettes; 2 VHS
  This series contains materials documenting A Day With(out) Art, an annual event on December 1 launched by Visual AIDS in 1989 to coincide with World AIDS Day, which involves activities and events at partnering arts organizations, museums, and galleries. The series includes promotional materials produced by Visual AIDS, such as press releases, funding requests, graphic logo designs, print advertisements, press clippings, correspondence, planning notes, and posters, many of which were utilized by the participating institutions.
  Additionally, the series contains materials focused on the institutions and organizations registered to participate in A Day With(out) Art through their own events, exhibitions, and activities. Materials include completed registration forms detailing the participant's events, as well as press clippings, photographs, and promotional items such as flyers, posters, and information sheets. For certain years, participant materials are further organized by specific cities or states, in addition to general event promotion files.
  This series also documents A Night Without Light, a companion event to A Day With(out) Art in which business and institutions turn out the lights in their buildings for 15 minutes on December 1 to commemorate the day. Materials for this event include promotional flyers, completed participant forms, and information kits, as well as photographs and postcard images. Proclamations from New York City honoring A Day With(out) Art and A Night Without Light over multiple years are also included. Additionally, the series contains the Every Ten Minutes recording created by Robert Farber for Visual AIDS in connection with A Day With(out) Art, as well as videos containing a public service announcement featuring students and a participant event.
  - Event Staff List, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Promotional Material, Print Advertisements, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 14, Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Posters, 1989 (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Participant Lists, Event Material (Includes Photographs), 1989 (Box 29, Folder 15-17, Box 30, Folder 1-3)
  - Press Clippings, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Event Scrapbook, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Kits, 1989-1990 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Steering Committee Material, May 15, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Brochures, Fact Sheets, Press Releases, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Print Advertising and Related, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
  - Posters, Postcard, Advertising Billboards-Related, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 3-4, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Participant Lists and Completed Forms, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 5-8, Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Questionnaires Regarding Canadian Participants, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Participant Event Material (Includes Photographs), 1990 (Box 32, Folder 3-5, Box 33, Folder 1-2, Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Press Clippings, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 3, Box 66, Folder 4)
  - AIDS Timeline -- Notes, Print Material in Publications, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 4, Box 34, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Timeline -- Print Material in Publications, Proofs, 1990, 1991, 2013 (Box 66, Folder 5, Box 69, Folder 2-3)
  - Night Without Light -- Photograph, Postcards, Promotional Material, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Names Project Partnership -- Correspondence, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Bravo Television "Moment Without Television" -- Press Releases, Promotional Material, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Bravo Television "Talkin' About AIDS" and Other Programming -- Press Releases, Promotional Material, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 5)